

GODFREY SAMUEL

Software Engineer

♥: +2348082358376 区: godfreysam09@gmail.com •: Abuja-Nigeria

ABOUT ME

Over the past three years, I have worked on projects and serviced clients which have helped me honed my skill as a software engineer and web developer.

I have developed a good track record with technologies such as HTMI, CSS, Jquery and JavaScript both on the frontend and backend using Node.js, Express.js and Handlebars as template engine for server-side rendering, I have also worked with databases such as NEDB for in-memory data storage and management, MongoDb and Mongoose for larger datasets at the backend, Graphql, Axios and browser inbuilt fetch API.

I believe I have a lot to offer as an engineer who has been working hard at his craft; I have a quick grasp of new concepts and technology which is why I am working hard to build a successful career as a software engineer and hopefully be reckoned with as an expert in my field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Esty Telecom

Entry level | Software developer Abuja, Nigeria 2020-01-01 | 2020-09-01 Software developer, and Data sorting

Founder epinsorter.com

2021-01-01

Programmer, Full stack Software engineer.

EDUCATION

Degree: Bachelor of Science Engineering Physics

2012-11-10 | 2016-04-15

Obafemi Awolowo University Ile-Ife, Nigeria.

JOB SKILLS

Software Development

Full Stack Web Developer

JavaScript API'S and Markup

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English

Local Dialects

CERTIFICATES & AWARDS

Responsive Web Design: Certificate | 2019

JavaScript Algorithm and Data Structures: Certificate | 2020

Front End Libraries: Certificate | 2020

Google Cloud: Certificate | 2021

PROJECTS & PORTFOLIO

My Portfolio: http://godfreyo.link/